You're a funny green bee.
你是一只有趣的绿色蜜蜂
Green bee?
绿色蜜蜂
You are seeing the world for the first time!
你肯定是第一次看这个世界了
Pardon me, little miss.
原谅我   小姐
Flip the grasshopper is my name. Roaming the meadow is my game.
Flip草蜢就是我的名字 在草地上漫步就是我的游戏
What's the meadow?
什么是草地
Kid, you got to get out more. Hee-ho!
孩子   你需要多点走出来看看   嘿呵
There it is.
就是那里
The meadow, my home.
草地   我的家
You live out here?
你住在那里吗
Not just me. Lots of insects live in the meadow.
不仅仅是我   许多昆虫都住在草地上
Big, small, funny, smelly.
大的   小的   有趣的   臭的
You name it. It's everything you can see,
只要你说得出来   你就可以看得到
up, down, sky to ground from your hive to the tulip beds, all the way to Gorgo's hedge,
上面   下面   从天上到地下   从你的蜂窝到郁金香的花床 一直到Gorgo的树篱
where no little bee should ever go.
那里是小蜜蜂不能去的
Why?
为什么
Because a giant bug-eating monster named Gorge lives there.
因为一只叫Gorgo的巨大的吃虫子的大型怪物 住在那里
But enough of that!
就说到这里吧
Where are your friends?  Bees always travel in groups.
你的朋友们呢 蜜蜂通常都是三五成群的
I don't think I have any friends.
我不觉得我有任何朋友
No one in the hive likes me.
在蜂窝里的蜜蜂都不喜欢我